&gt;&gt; So, we just saw an example where the decision boundary was really,
لقد رأينا للتو مثالاً كان فيه حد القرار
really complicated.
.معقدًا بالفعل
So, we have a situation like this.
.لدينا موقف مثل هذا
We call this overfitting and it's a common phenomena in machine learning that
نسمي ذلك ملاءمة زائدة وهي ظاهرة شائعة في التعلم الآلي
you have to be always aware of every time we do machine learning.
.يجب أن تكون على دراية بها دومًا في كل مرة نقوم بالتعلم الآلي
To give an example, if you look at the data over here,
،لضرب مثال، إذا نظرت إلى البيانات الموجودة هنا
it seems to be linearly separable.
.تبدو قابلة للفصل خطيًا
A decision surface between red and blue, it looks like this.
.خدمة القرار بين الأحمر والأزرق، تبدو مثل ذلك
Correctly classifies the red data, but looks erratic at many other places.
.البيانات باللون الأحمر هي المصنفة على النحو الصحيح، لكن تبدو غريبة في العديد من الأماكن الأخرى
That happens when you take your data too literal,
،يحدث ذلك عندما تأخذ البيانات فعليًا
and when your machine learning algorithm produces something as complex this,
،وعندما تقوم بمعالجة شيء معقد مثل هذا آليًا وإنتاجه
as opposed to something as simple as this you are over-fitting.
.في مقابل شيء بسيط مثل ذلك فأنت تقوم بملاءمة زائدة
So, in machine learning we really want to avoid over-fitting.
.في التعلم الآلي، نريد بالفعل تجنب الملاءمة الزائدة
&gt;&gt; One of the ways that you can control over-fitting is through the parameter of
&gt;&gt; إحدى الطرق التي يمكنك من خلالها التحكم في الملاءمة الزائدة هي عبر معلمة
your algorithm.
.الخوارزمية
So, in SVM we have several parameters we've talked about.
.لذا، في SVM لدينا العديد من المعلمات التي تحدثنا عنها
C, gamma and the kernel come to mind.
.C وجاما ونواة تأتي على خاطري
So, which of these do you think affect the over-fitting potential of an SVM?
لذا، أي من هذه تعتقد أنها تؤثر على إمكانية الملاءمة الزائدة لـ SVM؟
Click as many as you think might be correct.
.انقر فوق أي عدد تعتقد أنه صحيح